<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SaiLog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SaiLog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:32:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NESRM Init</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nesrm-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:32:22 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nesrm-init/</guid>
      <description>NESRM | What and Why The &amp;ldquo;Never Ever Stable&amp;rdquo; Relationship Manager is an idea that I&amp;rsquo;ve been mulling over for a while now. I have a very specific use case that most CRM&amp;rsquo;s can&amp;rsquo;t model for me, atleast cheaply. All the different ideas and tasks can get overwhelming, so I hope trying to write some of it down might help.
The Challenges &amp;amp; Solutions 1. Database A lot of this begins trivial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devlog Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:36:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-projects/</guid>
      <description>This theme auto generates pages and subpages and directories to handle the menu items for tags and categories. I tried used categories and changing the front end to be projets, but the auto generation keeps overwrting what I do. This is annoying. How do I make the autogeneration conform to my new projets folder or stop this overwrite god</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devlog Hosting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:49:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Well I don&amp;rsquo;t remember where the old project was hosted, but let&amp;rsquo;s figure out where to host this one, and hopefully get some CI going so keeping this up-to-date isn&amp;rsquo;t a pain.
Github I got this git repo pushed to github.com/sai-sy/devlog so we&amp;rsquo;re good to go
Cloudflare I got a Cloudflare page up, now I need to make sure the CI is working. I think we have lift off for the devlog though</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakout Init</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/breakout-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:46:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/breakout-init/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m trying to use the wonderful Learn OpenGL resource to make a breakout game in C++</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devlog Init</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:15:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/devlog-init/</guid>
      <description>This is a third attempt at making a blog I&amp;rsquo;m happy with and keep up with. Currently there&amp;rsquo;s too much learning too do, too many tests, too many contracts, too many categories. I can&amp;rsquo;t keep up. Is this what eery developer deals with. Maybe just anyone and everyone. Or maybe I&amp;rsquo;m not cut out for the lifestyle I claim to partake in. Either way I need some way to jot things down.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
